great to see you man everything go huh
good I brought you a little cap oh yeah
I know you like winners yeah I
appreciate that thank you very much yeah
I do like what is here
I really really appreciate that I I
could tell something something was
bothering you just then but I didn't
know what it was I did I didn't know if
I was rooting for a different football
team or if I know what it was I didn't
always bother me but that was pensioned
forget about it and just
one
move on to something else sir I don't
know what yeah but thank you for the Hat
I appreciate that I got I got a bumper
sticker for you
I'm searching people thank you for that
he loved that yeah thank you so