ah how's it going
my name is Matt have you ever done
anything so cool so radical so brave
that you deserved a medal me neither
this is try not to feel inadequate and
and useless as a human being
challenge
[Music]
it's always in Russia isn't it well what
happens in in that in that country its
player unknown battlegrounds a live
simulator of Russia I don't get it I
mean it's cool they're all working
together and all but I mean I'm sure the
dog was fine
all right let's see something impressive
what is this were they catching oh my
god was that a bad bit what was the baby
trying to kill himself
man it starts young Jesus Christ that's
crazy that baby had so much to live for
I'm making where is little weird for me
to joke about let's move on
you know those clickbait I almost died
videos which I would never make this is
the only one this is the only youtuber
I've actually seen almost died FPSRussia
I remember he said maybe we'll shoot we
can shoot this and get a lo a bit of
shrapnel look at that fucking shit that
would have fucked him up so good that
perfectly calm calm hair would have been
a little messy I think if that hit him
all right what have we got are they
stuck together
[Applause]
whoa what the fuck happened was that his
spare a parachute Jesus Christ this
making me so fucking anxious yeah
I'm never going parachuting whatever is
called aim worse than man ain't worth
day I'm happy right here in front of my
computer you know a I don't understand
why anyone will leave your computer at
any point doesn't make I don't get it
you know I don't get it but let's watch
more people fuck up all right it's
almost at the oh shit
dandy are you good how can you laugh
that off I would need therapy what the
fuck he's got almost completely
destroyed he would have broke his
fucking neck look at that he would have
felt anything oh it hurts how is the guy
just filming it I would be like oh my
fucking god look it's just like oh yeah
it's gonna go YouTube it's gonna be
great my friend is dying I'd be like
yeah what the fuck
well that's another thing off the list
I'm never going climbing that's great
everyone looks like I'm never about to
go baseball gaming when I was taking a
look at this yes for this young man
right here oh yeah it was looking at a
pretty girl hit him right inside of the
head you're in the front row you're not
even paying attention what the fuck was
this young man right here they saved my
dad it was huge densify pretty well I'm
not going baseball either thank you very
much
fuck man why is like so dangerous I
don't like it I like it at all okay what
is this it's a skunk but the level to
hell man with my baby you can do this
you can do a good play good boy good boy
Oh
oh I was waiting for him to spray him
sorry Jesus Christ fuck you man I don't
know who I've seen this one this one is
insane man el perro
that's dogging in the Transylvanian
oh they never I just fit in detective
[Music]
there is a God after all oh my man oh my
god another one Jesus Christ how the
fuck did not at least one person die
there
I'm sorry but gee look at these idiots
sitting on the edge at a curb
oh my god Amit oh my god
they don't even move they get I'm like
I'm comfortable here I guess oh my god
oh I'm sorry but I kind of want one of
them to die I'm there's going to be
there's going to be a war with that
movie called there's definitely going to
be a final destination where all of them
died like the dentists or some shit and
said you know what I mean
yeah that's right fuck man it's making
me so anxious this shit alright what is
this what could possibly happen here the
fuckers with the course everywhere damn
damn I will never do anything that cool
and neither will you
let's just accept it we're watching for
you I'm I am PewDiePie and you're
watching PewDiePie it's pretty we're in
a pretty low space in our life the fuck
is happening here he's helping his
friend oh my god can he do it though
come on turtle come on that's the tour
choice sorry there you go that's awesome
because it's more testing fucking nipple
looks look at him he's like I got you
fam don't worry about it oh not too rich
see concrete evidence that global
warming isn't real I don't understand
how people still dispute it it's
ridiculous look at these tortoises just
look at that explain that shit
that's right you can't okay what did we
get oh god someone's gonna jump are they
oh shit oh shit oh shit
whoa that's pretty awesome that's really
awesome
I hope they gave them the men help
respect respect to that public service
worker you know he's actually paying
attention he's doing his job he sees the
guy that's it warms my heart to see
stuff like this what am I looking at
here oh shit he's choking just doing
Heimlich what are you doing look at that
girl oh the guy okay he knows there you
go there you go dry hump him he did it
see any any reason you have for dry
humping someone a stranger randomly I
would take learn how to do everyone
right now just Google Heimlich maneuver
and and learn that shit cuz this is
pathetic look at these fucking friends
oh you're fine buddy just shake it off
look at this girl yeah here you here you
go that's not gonna do shit you got it
you got it you gotta stop stop it legit
be cool if everyone just took some time
and learn how to do this shit properly
because that could really save someone's
life instead of instead of this pathetic
shit that you know if those were my
friends
I'd be like hahaha okay goodbye
unexpended
ah great fuck that
jeez it pisses me up it really pisses me
off seeing fucking idiots like this and
what do I do
I've seen this one fucking spaz Oh
people just have so much luck I don't
like it I don't
like it I'm never that I'm never this
lucky ah for fuck's sake are you fucking
kidding me okay now I just want someone
to get hurt at little bit just a little
bit please god damn it
whoa whoa oh they haven't even seen it
what the cat is a badass what the fuck
oh shit oh my god oh my god
she didn't see it until now what the
fuck oh poor cat Oh bless that cat got a
trip of a lifetime
the fuckers I can't do it he died yes
finally someone isn't that right Eggert
goddamn it you're the layman your lamer
pets and flippy I swear to God Wow okay
we're going to end episode there leave a
like every like pet gets saved from ice
that's right thank you very much I see
you Brooks tomorrow in another episode
if staying for sister Pfister