hi I'm Sal Khan founder of the
not-for-profit Khan Academy and I have
some very exciting news the data is in
from our first year of the partnership
between us and the College Board around
Khan Academy being the official practice
for the SAT and what we're seeing is
students who spend an average of 20
hours of practice on Khan Academy are
seeing roughly a hundred fifteen point
gain between the PSAT and the SAT and to
put that into perspective that's roughly
twice the point gain that students
typically see between the PSAT and the
SAT and what's especially heartening is
that we're seeing that game be
consistent across gender race and
socio-economic groups and so this makes
us feel really good not just from the
Khan Academy's point of view or the
College Board's point of view but just
in the overall theme of being able to
help level the playing field students
take the PSAT they can sync those
accounts with the Khan Academy Khan
Academy software then has the
information necessary to essentially do
a weak point training know where you
need practice not just in math but in
reading and writing as well and you get
that practice so that you can put your
best foot forward not just on the SAT
but to be optimally prepared for college
and for life so this is exciting news
it's also just the beginning and we hope
to work with all of you students parents
teachers to further level the playing
field for college and life access